The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Elders of the Soul Refining Sect,
come out and fight me !
This...
This is...
There are so many souls !
Only under the pressure of a Soul Transformation cultivator
can my Origin Soul finally recover.
The Soul Formation Elders have emerged !
You sure have guts !
Scram !
Such an intense Soul Formation killing intent...
Summon the Ancestor.
Insolent brat !
Devour !
Little friend,
this old man has waited a long time for you.
Paying respects to the Ancestor.
He really is Soul Transformation !
The 9 of you can leave.
Little friend Ceng Niu,
this old man has waited 2 years for this day.
If even Liu Mei could find me,
it isn't strange for the Soul Refining Sect's Ancestor
to know who I am.
I've been watching you lately,
you've been having a hard time.
For our meeting today,
I’ll first give you a small gift.
We’ll discuss details later.
Junior Liu Mei,
you have 10 breaths to get out of my Soul Refining Sect !
If you don't,
even if you’re the Suzaku’s disciple,
I’ll still kill you !
Scram !
Senior,
Junior has orders from my master
and I didn’t harm the Soul Refining Sect...
Why are you acting like this ?
6 breaths !
if Junior just leaves like this
and my master asks what happened,
I’ll have to tell him of this matter.
If he were to get angry...
4 breaths !
This is...
the Billion-Soul Flag !
Little friend Ceng Niu,
how was that small gift ?
What kind of small gift is this ?
Senior is willing to offend Suzaku.
Junior isn't happy but afraid.
Zhuque Zi is old,
he can’t make the entire planet listen to him anymore.
What does Senior want ?
You can just tell me.
Not so fast,
that was only the first gift.
Ceng Niu, you sought me out
to use the pressure of my cultivation
to heal your Origin Soul.
I will now grant that wish !
Is this enough ?
Not enough !
And now ?
Still not enough !
Alright,
it has been over 200 years
since this old man last used celestial spiritual energy.
I'm spending a lot
on this second gift !
Good !
Your cultivation was restored to Middle stage Soul Formation
and is even stronger than before.
Thank you, Senior.
It's a bit too early to be thanking me,
this old man has a third gift for you.
Do you dare to receive it ?
Why wouldn’t I ?
Sit down cross-legged.
This is the Soul Refining Sect’s main artifact: the Billion-Soul Flag.
With this artifact,
I even dare to fight against Ascendant cultivators !
Now,
I’ll use its soul power
to raise your cultivation to Late stage Soul Formation !
As for your domain,
you must comprehend it yourself.
These souls
are all at Soul Transformation level !
When they were about to die,
every Soul Transformation Ancestor of our sect
gave up their body to become a soul fragment of the Billion-Soul Flag.
You have to remember that when I die,
you must add my soul fragment into the flag as well…
Absorb as much as you can,
this old man isn’t stingy.
Soul power,
unleash !
Not bad,
although your domain remains at Middle stage Soul Formation,
your spiritual energy has reached Late stage.
Wang Lin's avatar
Late stage Soul Formation
Little friend Ceng Niu,
have you absorbed enough from this third gift ?
Senior, you said I can absorb as much as I want ?
Of course.
This little guy's body is already full of spiritual energy.
Even if he wants to absorb more,
he shouldn't be able to...
Original body, let us both absorb !
The original body walks the path of the Ancient Gods,
which survived by devouring spiritual energy.
Its need for spiritual energy
is several times greater than the avatar's...
He is back to absorbing energy now !?
But it seemed like he couldn't absorb anymore...
Well, well,
I made a promise...
Little friend Ceng Niu,
you really didn’t hold back...
Thank you for the 3 gifts Senior.
Is there anything
that Senior needs ?
Junior will do his best to fulfill it.
Good.
I'm glad you said that,
it means I did choose the right gifts.
Follow me !
Inside the Blood Ring
Soul Refining Sect
Little friend Ceng Niu,
the reason I gave you these gifts
is very important.
If you hadn’t come to my Soul Refining Sect,
I would’ve gone out to search for you.
Junior has heard that
there is a rumor that I killed a Soul Refining Sect Elder.
I assumed Senior was looking for me.
It's just a cover story.
If I were to look for you
for no reason,
it would attract too much attention.
What is it that requires Senior
to be so careful ?
Little friend Ceng Niu,
do you know why planet Suzaku
has less that 10 rank 5 cultivation countries ?
Long ago,
Suzaku became a rank 6 cultivation country
and was granted this planet by the Cultivation Alliance.
When they migrated here,
they found the planet was inhabited by powerful natives,
the Forsaken Immortal Clan.
What followed was a long and bloody war.
The cultivators won at great cost.
The Billion Soul Flag
was crafted during that war.
The first Suzaku of the country of Suzaku
made Mount Suzaku
the central operation center of planet Suzaku.
The 6 major sects of the country of Suzaku
formed the original 6 rank 5 cultivation countries of the planet.
Our Soul Refining Sect was one of the founding countries.
After that,
disciples from these sects scattered
and formed numerous cultivation countries across planet Suzaku.
Becoming a rank 6 cultivation country
has been my Sect's dream for generations.
But all these years,
whenever someone was about to reach Ascendant
they would be crippled overnight.
Now,
Soul Refining Country
we've even lost our country.
and are forced to operate as a sect.
Soul Refining Sect
Country of Pilu
Country of Suzaku
This is because all the previous Suzakus
have prevented any rank 5 country
from reaching rank 6
by fear they'd be overthrown
and would lose control of the planet.
But...
Junior is merely a Soul Formation cultivator.
How is any of that related to me ?
It is related to you.
You are one of Yunque Zi's candidates
to become the next Suzaku.
Yunque Zi ?
Him !?
Yunque Zi is Zhuque Zi's Junior Brother.
You gave me the gifts
because of him ?
Not entirely.
Little friend, are you willing to enter my Soul Refining Sect
as my successor ?
So that one day
my Soul Refining Sect can become a rank 6 cultivation country !
Why me ?
Since we've arrived on planet Suzaku
up to this day,
we've produced 36 Soul Transformation cultivators !
All their souls reside in this Soul Flag.
My Senior Brother was the 36th
and I will be the 37th.
Two years ago,
my Senior Brother sacrificed his lifespan to unleash his foresight domain.
He sought a path of survival for our sect
but in the end, he failed.
The moment he died
is the moment you stepped at the door of the sect !
It may be a coincidence.
Or it may not.
But with my lifespan ending, I must gamble
and believe my Senior Brother's domain succeeded
by bringing you to our sect !
Our sect has no worthy successors,
when I die
Suzaku will claim the Billion-Soul Flag.
Without it,
the Soul Refining Sect is doomed.
When my lifespan ends,
this flag will be yours.
Will you fulfill my request ?
Raising a country to rank 6
with Junior's cultivation
is nearly impossible.
Success or failure will depend on fate.
Junior will do his best !
I can protect you for 10 years.
After that, you're on your own.
This jade slip contains the Soul Sealing spell
Soul Sealing jade slip
as well as the method to control the Billion-Soul Flag
and the sect's core secrets.
From now on,
you're the only core disciple of the Soul Refining Sect !
Thank you Ancestor.
I must enter seclusion
to prepare my soul for the flag before I die.
Don't go farther than 10 000 li of the sect.
Note: 1 li = 500m
If you ever are in danger,
I need to be able to help you in time.
Don't worry Senior,
if I couldn't take care of myself,
I wouldn't have survived this long.
Junior has unfinished business
that needs to be settled.
I'll return to the Soul Refining Sect
before you come out of seclusion.
Since you are sure,
I'll say no more.
Wang Lin's original body
3-stars Ancient God
After absorbing the wood spirit,
the Heaven Defying Bead
only lacks the metal element.
Li Yuanfeng of Xue Yue,
Giant Demon Clan's Ancestor,
and Sun Tai, who took the opportunity to seal me.
I need to repay you all
for what you did to me !
Since I fought Sun Tai's lightning,
I've been severely injured.
This is all because of that damned Ceng Niu !
Have you found Ceng Niu's body ?
No trace of it yet...
All of you are useless !
Li Yuanfeng !
Ceng Niu...
“Original body… Let us both absorb!” Wang Lin called out to his original body in his heart.
This call crossed a long distance. At this moment, the original body in Chu opened his eyes.
The two purple stars on the original body began to spin.There was no longer a primary or secondary body between the original and the avatar; both were Wang Lin. It was as if he was split in half. When they fuse, they will become the real Wang Lin.
There was a mysterious connection between the avatar and the original body, which was why the original body was hurt when his Origin Soul collapsed. Through the same mysterious connection, the original body was absorbing spiritual energy from his avatar like crazy.
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.